-= 国语字幕组 群号：168755230 =-
荣誉出品
字幕制作交流家园
双语制作:绿芽  字幕翻译：vlakovic    绿芽
二一二年二月二十三日 12:34:13
还有十分钟就开打……
Ten more minutes.
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
谁让你进来的，滚！
Get the fuck out of here!
停! 不! 不!不!
Stop! Nyet! Nyet! Nyet!
"Jrabbren"（俄语发音，一种软饮料）
"Jrabbren"
我说"krabren".
I said "krabren".
不! 不!
No! No!
应该念成：Jrabbren（带典型的俄语喉音发声）
Jrabbren.
J-j-j-- 我念不了这样的音啊！
J-j-j-- I can't say that shit!
嘿, 菲尔!
Hey, Phil!
我们要试多少次才能拍完这一条?
How many times we got to go through that?
我们能否改个词，换个发音呢?
Could we just change that last line?
你看到了，必须这样念。
We'll have to do it again.
操，老子不拍了!
Man, fuck this shit!
等等.
Hold on.
乔治... 听我说.
George... Listen to me.
你已经不再是拳击冠军了, 做人要低调点，好吗?
You're not the champ anymore, you understand me?
事实上，你现在已经身无分文了.
In fact, right now all you are is broke.
要知道，我们好不容易来到俄罗斯.
Now, we traveled a long way.
我一直在帮你重新开始.
I'm trying to get you back on your feet.
一直在帮你挣钱.
I'm trying to get you paid.
所以，帮个忙.
So do me this favor.
按他说的去做.
Please, just do what he asks.
拍另外一个镜头吧，好吗?
Let's give it another shot, huh?
- 但是-- - 不, 不, 不.
- But listen-- - No, no, no.
不要 "但是".
No "but listen".
你在做你分内的工作, 我们得保持微笑...
You just do your job, we smile...
和那些公司的傻鸟老板吃午饭...
go out to dinner with these corporate cocksuckers...
忍一忍，你就能挣大钱回家了.
and you go home a richer man.
# Money, money, money #
Whoa.
Hmm.
Oops!
我的顾客们等不及了.
Our customers are very excited.
该死的比赛何时开始?
When the hell does the fight start?
马上就开始了.
It should start any second.
下注情况如何?
What are we giving?
俱乐部的赔率是5比1, 押博伊卡胜.
The bets from the clubs are 5 to 1, Boyka.
不过，马尔科夫说的，这个和博伊卡打的新人相当厉害.
Markov says this, uh, new fighter is extremely good.
以前听说过这个人.
Heard that one before.
博伊卡! 博伊卡! 博伊卡!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
博伊卡! 博伊卡! 博伊卡! 博伊卡!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
博伊卡, 博伊卡!
Boyka, Boyka!
女士们、先生们晚上好.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
我们独家现场直播
Broadcasting live and exclusively...
在全俄及全欧洲范围内选拔“斗士” （监狱系统内的打擂台选手）.
to select establishments across Russia and Europe.
在今晚的比赛中...
In this evening's bout...
104公斤级的...
weighing in at 104 kilos...
挑战者来自西伯利亚的基洛夫监狱...
fighting out of Kyrov penitentiary in Siberia...
他具有14次全胜的纪录，还未尝过败绩...
with a record of 14 wins and no defeats...
犯有二级杀人罪的...
convicted of second degree homicide...
他就是...
our challenger...
阿卡迪・达维奇!
Arkady Daviiiic!
而他的对手是...
And defending his unbeaten run...
34次压倒性胜利、未尝败绩的...
of 34 consecutive fights without defeat...
犯有多项一级杀人罪指控的...
convicted of 3 counts of homicide in the first degree...
92公斤级的...
weighing in at 92 kilos...
我们无可争议的冠军...
our own undisputed champion...
尤里・博伊卡! 博伊卡, 博伊卡, 博伊卡!
Uri Boyka! Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
博伊卡, 博伊卡!
Boyka, Boyka!
博伊卡, 博伊卡, 博伊卡!
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
博伊卡, 博伊卡!
Boyka, Boyka!
博伊卡! 博伊卡! 博伊卡!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
先生们, 比赛规则是...
Gentlemen, remember...
不许咬人、不许插眼睛、不许扯头发.
no biting, no eye gouging, and no hair pulling.
开始!
Fight!
Uh!
Unh! Ah!
- Uh! Argh! - Ah!
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
- Ha! - Unh!
Argh!
- Argh! - Boyka!
Aaah!
Uh!
Ugh! Uh!
Argh!
Unh! Oh!
Bah!
博伊卡, 博伊卡!
Boyka, Boyka!
合作愉快
To success!
他来了.
Here he is.
我去找他.
Excuse me.
乔治，你已经迟到一个小时了.
George, you are an hour late for the dinner.
不好意思，我把这事忘了.
Oh, my bad. I forgot all about this dinner.
查伯先生
Mr. Chambers.
广告的进展实在让人恼火.
The ad execs are getting pissed off.
进去喝一杯，跟他们沟通下，快.
Come in. Have a drink. We'll go.
好吧. 让我换件衣服.
All right. Let me change clothes.
- 给我10分钟. - 10分钟?
- Gimme 10 minutes. - 10 minutes?
在这个节骨眼上?
On top of an hour?
听着，这种扯蛋的公关事务--
Hey, listen, this brown nosing and breaking bread bullshit--
是你的工作. 我已经做好了我该做的.
That's your job. I did mine already.
我不想鸟他们.
They can kiss this ass.
告诉你, 等个20分钟吧.
Tell you what, 20 minutes.
Raah!
Argh!
Uh!
Unh! Uh!
Ah!
Argh!
- Unh! - Yes!
- Unh! - Argh!
Argh!
起来! 搞定他!
Get up! Finish him!
现在!
Now!
Aaaah!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
Unh!
Uh! Oh!
Argh!
Uh! Ugh!
你们在我的房间搞什么鬼--
What the fuck are you doing in my--
Ugh!
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
停!
Stop!
Boyka, Boyka!
Argh!
Uh!
Unh!
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
Raaah!
Raah!
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
给.
There.
如果我们不能找个牛人来对抗博伊卡...
If we cannot get better odds against Boyka...
我们就不得不在来年春天关门大吉.
we will have to shut down by spring.
赔不起了，靠！
It cannot keep going on like this.
放心吧，我已经想到办法了.
Don't worry. It won't.
乔治，他们说没人看到有暴徒侵犯你.
They said nobody saw these guys, George.
什么？难道他们没有监控的摄像头?
What, they ain't got no surveillance cameras out here?
我不知道.
I don't know.
你不会认为是我自己打自己吧.
You really don't think I did this shit.
又赢了一场，冠军?
Another easy fight, eh, champ?
没有人能打败你，是吧?
No one's ever gonna stop you, huh?
当你离开这里的时候...
When you get out of here some day...
你会成为基辅（乌克兰首都）最富有的人.
you'll be the richest man in Kiev.
我只是希望你记得我曾为你服务过--
I just hope you'll remember me--
Aah!
对不起，这是意外.
It was an accident.
把你的手拿过来.
Put out your hand.
不要.
No.
博伊卡.
Boyka.
你在听吗?
Did you hear?
听什么?
Hear what?
他马上要来了.
He is coming.
警察已经在他的房间里.
The police is already in his room.
他明天就到这.
He'll be here tomorrow.
Aaah!
这是你的圣经吗?
This is your Bible?
是的，警官.
Why, yes, sir.
我随身携带圣经.
I take the Good Book with me everywhere I go.
哦.
Mmm.
这个东西不是我的.
That is not mine.
那么这个也不是你的东西了.
Then this must not be yours, too.
对，不是我的.
No, it isn't.
你搞毛啊?
What the hell is going on here?
他们陷害我.
They're setting me up.
美国拳击手乔治・查伯被移往...
American boxer George Chambers has been transferred...
一座戒备森严的监狱内等待审判.
to a maximum security jail to await charges.
他六年前因为有争议的人身攻击行为 而被指控……
Convicted of a controversial assault charge 6 years ago...
这个前世界轻量级拳击冠军也曾被警告，因为...
the former Heavyweight Champion of the World was also cautioned...
拥有过量的非法止痛药片，在1993年的时候.
in 1993 over the possession of illegal painkillers.
可靠消息指出这次他涉案的毒品数量...
Our sources have indicated that the quantity...
超过了俄国法律规定的界限...
of narcotics involved is well over the threshold...
他将面临贩毒的指控.
for a trafficking charge.
这是马丽亚・阿隆索发自俄罗斯的报道.
This is Maria Alonso reporting from Russia.
他刚到了.
He just arrived.
看什么看?
Fuck are y'all lookin' at?
Yeah.
晚上好，查伯先生.
Good evening, Mr. Chambers.
我相信你一路上过得并不舒服.
I trust your journey wasn't too uncomfortable.
现在，我们再谈这个没鸟意思了.
Now, you and I both know you don't give a damn how my journey was.
我知道你以前进过监狱...
I understand you have been to prison before...
在你美国老家.
in the United States.
呵呵，你不要假装不知道...
And don't pretend that you don't know...
我是谁.
who the hell I am, either.
我可是你的超级粉丝...
I was a big fan of yours...
为你辉煌的职业生涯倾倒.
during height of your career.
事实上，我们很高兴能在这看到你.
In fact, we all are very excited you are here.
别太兴奋了, 因为我打算尽快离开这里...
Don't get too excited, 'cause I plan on walking...
一旦这桩鸟事有了个结果.
straight outta here as soon as this shit's straightened out.
可能吧.
Perhaps.
但是，同时...
But in the meantime...
你应该知道在这种地方...
you should know that in this facility...
我们非常渴望“斗士”.
we think very highly of fighters.
事实上，我们已经培养出了自己的冠军.
In fact, we even have our own champion.
你没听我说话, 克林克上校.
You ain't hearing me, Colonel Klink.
我已经说过了，我不会在这呆太久.
I told you. I don't plan on staying here long.
操！把水加热。
Fuck y'all. Heat this shit up.
你现在开始洗澡.
You take shower now.
操你妈的.
Go...fuck...yourself.
Ugh!
Argh! Ow!
Hmm.
Ha ha ha!
冠军，这是博伊卡给你的礼物，热腾腾的尿.
Champ, gift from Boyka. Warm piss.
- Unh! - Ugh!
Argh!
Ugh!
Unh!
Argh!
Oh!
没事吧, 伙计?
Are you all right, chum?
转过身去，别让老子看到你!
Turn around, get the fuck out of my face!
好吧.
Got it.
操! 这里真恶心!
Ugh! This is bullshit!
我不想打扰你，但是...
I don't mean to bother you, but...
你最好快点起床.
you better get up.
知道吗，如果你现在不离开这个房间...
Look, if you don't leave your cell...
等会他们就会锁门的.
when they unlock the door, they'll lock it again.
意味着你这一天都要困在这，出去不了.
You won't eat or get air for the rest of the day.
没有什么事……
Not that either of those things...
比不呆在这更让人愉快了.
are particularly pleasant out here.
伙计...
Yo, dude...
坦白讲.
Iet's get one thing straight.
我现在不想了解这里的垃圾规矩...
Now, I don't need to learn the ropes around here...
还懂?
you feel me?
好的，查伯先生.
Sure, Mr. Chambers.
当然理解.
Of course.
躲开!
Move!
老兄，你什么意思，你瞎了吧?
Hey, man, what the fuck? Man, you blind, too?
别介意.
Ignore him.
一个老疯子.
He's a bit crazy.
他被困在这太久了，懂我的意思吧?
Been here too long, you know what I mean?
平时在地下工作，只有到吃饭的时间才上来.
Lives underground. Only comes up here at mealtimes.
像“五星级宾馆待遇”，是不是?
Not exactly five star, is it?
不介意我坐在这和你一起吃吧?
Uh...do you mind if I join you?
嘿，老兄，你干吗老盯着我看?
Yo, dude, why do you keep staring at me like that?
不好意思.
I'm sorry.
只是--
It's just--
我无论如何都想不到...
Well, it's incredible that I'm sharing a cell...
能在这儿和大名鼎鼎的乔治・查伯共处一室.
with George Chambers here.
我叫斯蒂文・帕克.
Steven Parker.
我建议你马上站起来.
I suggest you stand up.
Unh!
我不是非要你这么干...
Look, I don't want to be pushy, man...
但你最好不要惹毛博伊卡.
but you don't want to mess with Boyka.
你,站起来!
You, stand!
站起来...快点!
You stand up...now!
Mmf!
- Unh! - Ugh!
你就是博伊卡?
Boyka, huh?
真JB恶心的名字
Now, what kind of bitch ass name is that?
我知道你曾是了不起的冠军.
You were great champion. I know.
但那是很久很久以前的事了.
Long time ago. Long time.
在这里，我才是冠军.
But in here, I am the champion.
而你...
And you...
只是一砣屎--
You are just my bi--
Raaah!
来吧，操!
Let's go, motherfucker!
拉开他们! 拉开他们!
Bring it! Bring it!
老子揍死你！
Let's go right now!
操!
Fuck you!
为什么阻止我?!
Why did you stop me?!
你以为我会怕那个王八蛋吗?
You think I'm afraid of that fucking oaf?
尤里，我已经告诉过你，你会和他公开单挑的.
Uri, I told you you'll have your own shot at him.
我已经在揍他!
I had my shot at him!
但是你的手下阻止了!
And then your guards stepped in to save him!
你到底想帮谁?!
How do you think that looks?!
忍耐一下，我们会帮你的.
Look, we help.
我没有问你.
I didn't ask you.
你阻止不了我想做的任何事.
You cannot stop me from doing what I have to do.
没人想阻止你.
No one wants to stop you.
我们只想提醒你，我们的职责是确保...
We're just telling you we have to be sure...
单挑是在擂台上，而不是在食堂!
it is in the ring!
Argh!
情况不妙.
Some bad news.
俄国人拒绝了我们的保释请求.
They're not offering bail.
你通知洛山矶的鲁本没有?
Did you call Ruben in L.A.?
乔治，你要知道鲁本是美国律师.
George, Ruben is an American attorney.
他对这件事爱莫能助.
He can't help with this.
那你还找其他人了-- 听着.
Did you even call-- Listen.
你最好告诉我现在怎么解决这案子.
You better tell me something I wanna hear right now.
我去过美国大使馆.
I've already been to the embassy.
他们对解决这事挺乐观的.
They're very upbeat.
但是他们告诉我这事运作起来...
But they're telling me the process can take...
至少要一个月--
anywhere from a month--
一个月?!
A month?!
这算什么鸟办法?!
What the fuck you talking about?!
现在，菲尔，我向上帝发誓...
Now, Phil, I swear to God...
你最好回去帮我找一群律师来...
you better turn around and get me a team of lawyers...
然后把我从这鬼地方救出去!
and get me the fuck out of here!
我想帮你啊.
I will.
但这需要时间.
It's just gonna take a little bit more time.
你这该死的小丑!
You fucking clown!
你知道耗在俄国的监狱里是什么感觉吗?
You know what it feels like to be in here for nothing, huh?
你在忽悠我!
You're bullshittin' me!
耐心点，乔治! 我尽我所能!
Just be patient, George! I'm doing everything I can!
我亲爱的马尔科夫.
My dear friend, Markov.
事情进展如何?
So, where are we?
黑鬼正被激怒.
He's uncomfortable.
这是一个好的开始.
That's a good first step.
我不需要什么好的开始，我要他俩马上打起来.
I don't need first steps. I need them to fight.
他和博伊卡之间已经有打架的动力了.
There's already bad blood between him and Boyka.
我想他最终会和博伊卡单挑的.
I think he'll--he'll-- he'll fight.
- 你想? - 是的.
- You think? - Yeah.
哦，这真是一个惊喜.
Well, that's a nice surprise.
"想" 是远远不够的，马尔科夫
"Think" isn't good enough, Markov.
我现在就要比赛的事尽快搞定.
I have to start making arrangements now.
恩...好吧.
Eh...sure.
最大的麻烦是……
Th-th-the only problem is, eh,
那个白痴黑人想早点离开这，重获自由.
this idiot hopes he'll go free any day.
哦，这样啊...
Yeah...
这事我负责搞定.
Well, I'll handle that.
你负责把他俩弄上擂台.
You just take care of the fight.
-马尔科夫... - 啥?
- And Markov... - Yeah?
不要让我失望，记住了吗?
Don't disappoint me, ok?
我说, 够了!
I said, enough!
到底怎么了?! 你们想干嘛?!
What the fuck's going on?! Why are you doing this?!
Ugh!
Ow, unh!
Argh!
Ugh, uh!
Unh!
Aah!
Aaargh!
Ow!
Ugh! Unh! Ugh!
谢谢.
Thank you.
他们为啥打你?
What the hell was that about?
没什么.
Nothing.
但无论如何都要谢谢你.
But thanks for your help anyway.
毒虫（吸毒上瘾的人），你悠着点，
Well, don't take it personally, junkie.
我只是不想看到一群人欺负一个人罢了.
I just don't like seeing people getting bullied.
除非我也是其中的一员.
Unless it's me doing the bullying.
听我说, 查博先生...
Listen, Mr. Chambers...
你应该知道这里的一些规矩.
there's something you ought to know about this place.
当然，即使你有一天会离开这.
E-even when you're getting out any day, of course.
说?
What?
这里被黑道统治.
It's owned by the mob.
我的意思是有一个黑老大.
I mean... One man, really.
他控制一切，包括法律和警察.
He owns the cons, he owns the cops.
他叫卡卡.
Ha! He's name is Gaga.
哈哈!
Ha ha ha!
- 卡卡? - 是的.
- Gaga? - Yeah.
你为什么要告诉我这些?
So why are you telling me?
以防万一...
Just thought it best if--if--if--if you...
万一什么?
If I what?
简单地说.
Go with the program.
就是如何保护好自己.
Best way to stay healthy.
呵呵，我有自己的办法保护自己.
Hey! I got my own way of staying healthy.
怎么保护?
What's that?
狠狠地揍那些兔崽子...
Knock the other son of a bitch out...
如果他们敢惹我.
before he gets a chance to do it to me.
发生什么事了?!
What happened?!
什么?!
What?!
你敢在这为所欲为?!
You think you come in here and do what you want?!
操！这是我的地盘.
Fuck you! This is my world.
操你妈的！
Motherfucker, keep your world.
老子才不稀罕你的地盘.
I don't want this shit.
有种你别嚎叫
And anyway, why you talking to me right now, man?
咱们来干一场--
Either throw your hands or step the fuck--
- 好啊，来啊! - 操你妈的!
- If you're so tough, then fight me! - Bitch ass motherfucker!
到擂台上打!
In the ring!
操，我才不去擂台!
Man, fuck the ring!
就在这打.
We can do this shit right now.
操你这个SB!
Bitch-ass punk!
日，有种在擂台打!
Fuck you! Fight me in the ring!
痛快点! 就在这解决!
Right now! I'll take you right here!
- 来啊! - 来啊!
- Come on! - Come on!
还等什么?
What you got for me?
操!
Fuck you!
就在这打, 操你妈的，来啊!
I'll fight you right now, motherfucker! Come on!
- 到擂台上打! - 去你妈的!
- In the ring! - Fuck that!
你一次只能集中精神打一个人.
You have to concentrate on one fight at a time.
先别管那个美国黑鬼--
Forget the American--
闭嘴!做你的事!
Shut up! Do your fucking job!
什么鸟世界轻量级拳击冠军.
Heavyweight Champion of the World.
我会把他的头扭下来!
I'll rip his fucking head off!
是的，你当然会.
Of course you will.
但是今晚你会扭另外一个人的头, 好吧?
But tonight you rip someone else's head off, ok?
闭嘴!
Shut up!
博伊卡.
Boyka.
下注情况如何?
So what are the bets?
25万人押前三回合结束...
250,000 across the first 3 rounds...
只有20人押四至5回合结束.
and another 20 across 4 and 5.
情况还可以好点. 给我电话.
Could be a lot better. Give me the phone.
马尔科夫.
Markov.
搞定没?
What the hell's going on?
比赛将在15分钟内开始.
Fight starts in 15 minutes.
我现在正赶往现场.
I'm walking to the arena right now.
我不是谈这场比赛.
That's not what I'm talking about.
我是说你搞定那个黑鬼没?
What the fuck's going on with Chambers?
我们正在尽力，卡卡.
We're doing everything we can, Gaga.
再加把劲，加把劲，好吧？
You better do more, my friend. You better do more, understand?
好的.
Yes.
Boyka, Boyka!
Fight!
Unh!
Unh! Ugh!
Ugh!
Boyka! Boyka!
Raaah!
Unh!
Unh! Uh!
Arghhh.
Unh!
Raah!
Boyka!
Ugh!
Unh! Ah!
Uh!
Ow!
Argh! Argh!
Boyka!
Unh! Ow!
Argh!
Ow!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
Unh! Yaah!
Yah!
Ow!
Arrrrgh!
Unh! Unh!
Ow!
Unh!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
Boyka! Boyka!
Unh!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Stop! Stop!
Unh!
Unh! Unh! Unh! Unh!
Argh!
Unh!
监狱长要见你.
Warden wants to see you.
我现在唯一想见的人是美国大使.
Only person I wanna see is from the U.S. embassy.
你现在必须见狱长.
You see warden now.
Ugh!
操你妈的--!
Motherfuck--!
Ugh!
够了.
That's enough.
查伯先生...
Mr. Chambers...
你自己不断地给自己找麻烦.
you are making things very difficult on yourself.
我给你指出一条活路.
There's a way you can make your time here much easier.
你已经知道我们监狱的搏击冠军...
You've seen now our resident champion...
尤里・博伊卡有多牛B了.
Uri Boyka, in action.
我们想你和他之间来一场擂台赛.
We want to arrange a fight between the two of you.
我才不干!
I ain't fighting, man!
我不想参加这种狗日的马戏团杂耍...
I wouldn't take part in this circus brawl bullshit...
你安排的一切.
you got going on here anyway.
你叫那种鸟事什么?
The hell you call that shit?
运动吗?
A sport?
就像我说过的，如果你答应了...
As I was saying, if you fight...
你会发现事情完全不一样了...
you'll find that things could become...
比呆在这愉快多了.
much more pleasant around here.
或许，你甚至可以...
Who knows? You could even find yourself...
坐上回家的飞机.
on a plane heading home.
好，听着.
Fine. Have it your way.
你现在的工作是为整个监狱掏下水道.
Sewage duct for whole prison.
非常破旧.
Very old.
每天都堵塞的下水道.
Clogged every day.
干吧!
Go!
去你妈的!
Uh, hell no!
干!
Go!
把那东西拿开!
Get that shit out of my face!
去捡起来.
Go get it.
操!
Fuck you!
敬酒不吃，吃罚酒.
If you don't work, then we'll make you work.
嘿.
Heh.
什么?
What?
不要给那些“猩猩”任何整你的借口.
Don't give these gorillas an excuse.
不值得.
It's not worth it.
告诉我你的工作号.
Give me number.
在你的铁锹上.
On your shovel.
Eighteen.
18.
你每天干完活后记得把铁锹还我.
You bring it back to me when you've finished each day.
在还之前，一定记得把屎清理干净.
Make sure you clean the shit before you give it back.
吹得不错啊.
Not bad for an old Russian dude.
我经常练而已.
I've had time to practice.
天啊!
Oh, Christ!
你真臭.
Man, you truly stink.
去死吧.
Fuck you.
或许我应该戴个防毒面具.
Maybe I should ask for a gas mask.
你还可以申请换个房间.
Or maybe transfer to another cell.
那意味着你会失去与我聊天的乐趣，如何?
What, and miss out on my sparkling conversation?
貌似克罗特会让你不好过的哦.
Looks like Crot gave you quite a hard time.
谁?
Who?
轮椅上的那个家伙, 克罗特.
The guy in the wheelchair, Crot.
克罗特在俄语里是鼹鼠的意思. （比喻他在地下打洞）
Crot is Russian for mole.
你要了解...
You know...
那家伙曾是苏联红军的军官.
that guy used to be a commando in the Russian army.
他被关进来后相当凶悍.
I'm told that he was quite a mean motherfucker back then.
甚至杀了一个狱卒.
He even killed a prison guard.
你说那老家伙?
That old dude?
是的.
Yeah.
他会在地洞里被关一辈子的.
There's no way they're gonna let him out of this shit hole.
哦.
Hmm.
但是，你就不一样了...
But you, on the other hand...
你是少数能有机会从这脱身的人.
you're one of the lucky few that does have a way out.
是吗? 如何脱身?
Yeah? How so?
听马尔科夫的话，跟博伊卡打一场.
Take Markov's offer. Fight Boyka.
天啊, 难道你们不睡觉的?
Jesus, don't you guys ever sleep?
Aah!
看你那鸟样，毒虫.
Look at you, junkie fuck.
好痛--
C-can't--
Argh!
你应当庆幸你还活着.
You're lucky to still be breathing.
Unh.
如果那黑鬼还不答应打擂台的事，你就完了.
If he doesn't fight soon, your luck will end.
Ah!
我们给你带来博伊卡的口信.
We bring you a message from Boyka.
Argh!
Unh! Ow!
Ow!
Ugh!
Aah!
Argh!
嘿!
Hey!
Ugh!
Argh!
Ow!
Unh!
Oh!
Uh!
- Uh! - Uh!
Ow!
Argh!
走.
Move.
Ugh!
Argh!
好好呆着.
Enjoy your new home.
什么事?
What?
他被关进了水牢.
He's in the hole.
一个可以使人改变想法的地方.
People change their minds in that place.
做得好
Good.
Ugh.
Ow!
嘿
Hey.
站起来
Stand up.
站起来接这碗热汤
Stand up. I have soup.
这是药丸
Pills.
嚼着吞
Chew and swallow.
能降烧
Help with your fever.
你为什么要帮我？
Why are you doing this?
闭嘴，别废话
Shut up and drink.
还有面包
And take this, too.
嘿
Hey.
你为什么帮我？
Why are you doing this?
你为什么老是问个不停？
Why do you care why I do it?
因为我从一个从不免费帮人的地方来（美国）
'Cause where I'm from, ain't nothin' free. Why?
你从没帮过别人吗？
You never help anyone?
可能真没有吧
Probably not.
操！你不了解我
Motherfucker, you don't know me.
至少我给我妈购买了一幢豪宅
That's why I bought my mother a ten-bedroom house.
但我不会这么慷慨的对其他人
I don't do for nobody, shit.
但你也可以帮你自己
You probably do that for you, too.
你知道你的问题在哪吗，老家伙？
Hey, you know what your problem is, old man?
你被关太久了，已经变得很不现实了
You been here too long. You lost touch with reality.
呵呵，你的问题恰恰在于你太不现实了
Your problem is that you're not accepting reality.
现实是，我被人陷害
Reality is, I was framed.
我不属于这
I don't belong here.
我也不会在这呆太久的
And I ain't gonna be here much longer.
你还是没明白
You still don't understand.
他们不会让你轻易离开这的
They will never let you out of here.
把他捞起来清洁干净
Get him cleaned up.
这是白色大鲟鱼的顶级鱼子酱
It is Beluga caviar.
每千克要2万5千美圆
25,000 American dollars per kilo.
对我来说，这像老鼠屎
Looks like rat shit to me.
闻起来也像，呵呵
Smells like it, too.
你知道我是谁吗？查伯先生
Do you know who I am, Mr. Chambers?
你是“大狗”，对不对?
You're the big dog, right?
是的，我是“大狗”
Yeah. I'm the big dog.
汪、汪，呵呵
Ruff! Heh.
我是把你弄到这来的大狗
I am the big dog that brought you here.
那么……大狗先生……
So...Mr. Big Dog...
你难道就不怕我跳起来……
what makes you think I won't jump up there...
把你揍成一条死狗?
and make you a dead dog?
因为我相信你没那么笨
Because I know you're not stupid.
让我解释一下，查伯先生
Let me explain something to you, Mr. Chambers.
我是一个商人
I'm a business man.
而这就是一个商业运作
And, uh, this is a business situation.
请
Please.
我把你弄进来，也能把你放出去
I brought you here. I can let you out.
选择权……在你手里
The choice...is yours.
你想我和那个博伊卡鸟人在擂台上干一架，对吧？
You want me to fight that clown Boyka, right?
是的，这会让我很高兴
It will make me very happy, yeah.
如果我不答应呢？
And if I don't?
这样的话……
Well...
你会老死在这个监狱
you could end up in this place for a very long time.
运气好点的话，会遇上一次意外，早点超脱……
Maybe meet with an accident. Perhaps stay forever.
我已让我的人负责斡旋...
Well as we speak, I got my man working on turning...
会把整件事曝光在媒体面前
this thing into the biggest media circus you ever seen.
你的人?
Your man?
哪一位啊?
Which one is this?
我的经纪人
My manager.
菲尔，你他妈的站在那干吗--
Phil, what the fuck are you doing up--
听着，乔治，一切都会好起来……
Listen, George, everything is going to be all right.
卡卡有个伟大的计划
Gaga here has a great plan.
我们都会发财的
We're all gonna make a ton of money.
放屁！
Oh, shit.
他们告诉我整件事会很快解决的
They told me the whole thing would be quick.
你将在一周内重获自由
That you'd be out in a week.
一大笔钱啊，是我们梦寐以求的
The money is huge. It's what we've been waiting for.
你只要识时务，不要那么固执
You just need to stop being so goddamned stubborn...
去擂台上打一场
and take the fight.
操你妈的，老子要踢烂你的屁股！
Motherfucker! I'll kill your motherfuckin' ass!
你个王八蛋!
Backstabbing son of a bitch!
别傻了，打擂台吧！
Don't be stupid. Take the fight!
该死的，闭嘴！
Shut up, dead man! Shut the fuck up!
操！
Fuck you!
我有一个好消息
I have good news.
说
Tell me.
我太兴奋了，乔治
I'm so bloody excited, George.
为何？
Why?
为何?
因为你马上要和博伊卡打了
You're going to fight Boyka, that's why.
嘿...
Hey...
你不需要一个助手吗?
You don't need a cornerman, do you?
哦，你有适当的人选?
Why, you got somebody in mind?
乔治...
George...
我是这里你唯一能信任的人...
I'm the only one you can trust around here...
你知道的，对不?
you know that, don't you?
我能问你一个问题吗? 乔治
Can I ask you something, George?
什么?
What?
如果你离开这了...
If you got out of here...
你想干的第一件事是啥?
what's the first thing you'd do?
你的意思是“当”我离开这里的时候，对不?
You mean "when" I get out of here, right?
当然
Of course.
我还不知道，兄弟
I don't know, Stevie.
我想去看我老婆
I'd try to see my wife.
你结婚了?
You're married?
“应该”是吧
I like to think so.
她来这探望过你吗?
She ever visit you here?
来过一次
Once.
她现在另结新欢
She's got a boyfriend now.
一个做生意或干别的行当的
Commodities or something.
真不幸啊，兄弟
That's messed up, Stevie.
这样也好，不再心痛了
Doesn't hurt anymore.
你知道，有一段时间还是很痛苦的
Used to, you know?
现在结束了
Not anymore.
你何时才能离开这?
When are you getting out of here, man?
哦...
Ohh...
还有12年
twelve years.
真糟糕!
Damn!
兄弟...
Stevie...
你是否想过戒毒呢?
you ever think about cleaning your shit up?
为何而戒?
What for?
哦.
Wow.
兄弟，不要这样举着
See, Stevie, don't hold it like that.
应当这样举着
Hold it like this. You hold it like this...
你的肩膀与软垫之间要保持一定的距离
you'll rip your shoulder out of the socket.
像这样举着，还懂?
So hold it like that, you got it?
- 懂了 - 慢慢来
- I think so. - Don't worry.
好的，左
All right. Jab.
右
Cross.
左
Jab.
右
Cross... jab.
# I'm gonna crush you #
# Thank you much #
# You can't compete with me, I'm gonna flush you #
# Send you out to sea, so take a number, line 'em up #
# I'll cut you down like a tree, I'm gonna crush you #
# Flatten out your brain, gonna rush you #
# You gonna get such pain, they're gonna brush you #
# Dust you off the ring #
# Bow down low 'cause there can only be one king #
# I'm dropping bombs on you like a blitzkrieg crew #
# And you can't see through the fog of this storm of power #
# 'Cause I am the man of your life's last hour #
# You gonna feel my game until you scream #
Ugh.
醒醒
Hey. Hey.
醒醒!
Hey!
醒醒!!
Hey!!
你们想干嘛？
Oh, for fuck's sake, man.
我不是按你们的吩咐把事办妥了吗?
I did everything you asked, didn't I?
他不是答应比赛了
He's going to fight.
我们还有一件事要你做
We have one more job for you.
放聪明点?!
Understand?!
Ha ha ha!
做得如何?
How did I do?
还不赖
Not bad.
时间到
Time.
成功！
Let's do this.
我们伦敦的朋友...
Have our friend in London...
在博伊卡身上押了50万美圆
put half a million on Boyka.
搏卡?
Boyka?
但是，先生这里80%的钱都是押在美国人身上
But, sir, 80% of the money coming in is on the American.
随你怎么想，先生
Whatever you say, sir.
先生们!
Gentlemen!
一场你们期待已久的比赛
The fight you've all been waiting for.
右边是来自美国的选手...
To my right, fighting out of the United States...
拥有38次击倒对手的记录...
with a record of 38 victories...
未尝败绩...
and no defeats...
乔治...
George...
莱斯曼・查伯!
Iceman Chambeeeers!
左边是...
And to my left...
无需介绍的
a man who needs no introduction.
我们自己的……
Our...own...
无可争议的冠军...
undisputed champion...
尤里...
Uri...
搏卡!
Boyka!
Boyka! Boyka!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
先生们, 比赛规则是...
Gentlemen, remember...
不许咬人，不许插眼睛，不许扯头发
no biting, no eye gouging, and no hair pulling.
我会用你熟悉的拳击的方式打败你
I'll beat you at your own game.
只用拳头
Fists only.
不要在我身上溅太多血
Just don't bleed on me too much.
开始!
Fight!
Boyka! Boyka!
Uh! Uh! Uh!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
- Unh! Unh! - Ah!
Kill him! Come on! Come on! Kill him!
Unh! Unh! Unh! Unh!
Ow!
Mmf! Uh! Uh!
Unh!
Keep your hands up!
Ugh!
Unh!
Oh!
一!
One!
二!
Two!
三!
Three!
四!
Four!
Argh!
Hey!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
Boyka! Boyka!
Argh!
Yaah! Yaah! Yaah!
- Ugh! - Argh!
- Unh! - Yah!
Ow!
Yaah! Ugh! Ugh!
Argh!
Ugh!
毛巾
Towel.
桶
Bucket.
水
Water.
快点，斯蒂文
Come on, Stevie!
Argh!
Boyka! Boyka!
开始!
Fight!
- Unh! - Yaah!
Ugh!
Boyka! Boyka!
Unh!
Ugh, uh!
Ow!
Ugh!
Uh!
Boyka! Boyka!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
Uh!
Ugh!
发生什么事了?
What happened?
你被下药了
You were drugged.
斯蒂文
Stevie.
那个王八蛋
That motherfucker!
混蛋，你干的好事！
That's your ass, Stevie.
婊子养的!
You son of a bitch!
斯蒂文!
Stevie!
哦，不！
Oh...Ugh.
你怎么了!
Man!
斯蒂文，天啊！
Goddamn it, Stevie.
你个胆小鬼，站起来!
You fuckin' pussy, get up!
我是胆小鬼?
I am pussy?
哈哈哈!
Ha ha ha!
我是胆小鬼? 看看你的脸!
I am pussy? Look at your face!
你才是胆小鬼
You are a fuckin' pussy.
那场比赛不公正，你知道的
That fight was bullshit and you know it.
你让斯蒂夫下药，所以你赢了
You had Stevie drug me, and that's how you won.
我是世界上最好的战士
I am the best fighter in the world.
我不需要你那个毒虫朋友来帮我取胜
I do not need your junkie friend to help me win.
你能相信这个SB美国人说的话吗?
Can you believe this fuckin' American?
你给你的对手下药，还恬不知耻的说 自己是战士？
You drug your opponents and you call yourself a fighter?
我不知道你放什么屁
I do not know what you're talking about.
你给你自己的失败找借口
You make big excuse because you lose!
你应该很庆幸我没有打死你
You should be happy I did not finish you.
两位，冷静一下
You guys can't get enough of each other.
回到你的囚室
Move over back to your cell.
操！你答应过我，放我出去的
Man, fuck you! You said I'd get out.
乔治，我不知道有这么个说法
I know nothing about this arrangement, George,
但我会去了解一下
but surely, I'll look into it.
你个王八蛋骗子!
You lying mother--!
Ow!
你答应过我的，放开我，放开我！
You told me I was gonna get out of here! Get off me! Get off!
把他拖出去!
To the pole!
混蛋，我会揍扁你!
Ugh! I'm gonna have your ass, punk!
I'm gonna have your ass, punk!
混蛋，等我离开这我会揍扁你!还有你!
Wait till I get outta here! Yeah, you, punk! You!
马尔科夫! 操你妈--!
Markov! You motherfuck--!
干死你!
You understand what I'm--unh!
你他妈的!
You--! Unh!
Ow!
Ow! Ugh!
谣传……
There's a rumor.
美国人喝了被下药的水
The American was given a bottle of water with something in it.
我已经警告过你们
I'm told you know something about it.
博伊卡...不
Boyka...no.
这可是真的?
Is it true?
回复他
Answer him.
但是--
But--
看看这个!
Look at this!
看!
Look!
古埃及勇士!
Egyptians!
古希腊壮士! 少林武僧! 拳王阿里!
Greeks! Asians! American boxers!
他们把搏击带入科学的殿堂
All made fighting into a science.
Ugh!
而我则是下一个殿堂级人物
I am the next stage.
你会觉得我需要你...
And you think I need you...
去给我的对手下药?
to drug my opponents?
把这些垃圾打算干净
Wipe this fuckin' trash off my floor.
听我说
Listen.
当你计划释放查伯的时候，我很惊讶
I was wondering when you're planning on releasing him.
我的意思是，自从交易结束后……
I mean, since the deal is done.
了解，是你一开始就说过的
Since when did you start...
关于查伯的事吗，菲尔?
caring about Mr. Chambers, Phil?
哦，与他无关
Well, it's not that.
只是，你知道人总是喜欢问问题
It's just, people are starting to ask questions.
问题
Questions.
你想要什么，菲尔?
What do you want, Phil?
是这样，我要的是...
Well, given the, uh...
一些意外、一些耽搁需要点补偿啦...
unexpected hassles, the delays...
我还想要25万
I'd like another 250.
好的，再给你25万
Ah, ok. 250 it is.
太好了
Oh! That's great.
24万、25万
240. 250,000.
谢谢
Thank you.
是说再见的时候了
I guess this is good-bye, then.
一路顺风，“钱迷”先生
Have a nice trip, Mr. Gold.
谢了
Thank you.
Oh!
想干吗?
Now what?
看什么看?
What the hell you looking at?
我已经注意到...
It has been brought to my attention...
你们中有人多管闲事...
that a few of you have been interfering...
帮助了正在受罚的查伯
with the punishment of inmate Chambers.
那么，所有与此事有关的人...
All those responsible...
自觉举手站出来
identify themselves now by raising their hands.
向前一步!
Step forward!
还有谁?
Anyone else?
Ah-ha.
我明白了
I see.
真有趣
Very cute.
你们现在就站在这儿...
So now you'll stand out here...
在寒风中反思吧!
in the fucking cold and think about it!
闭嘴，我告诉过你不要乱来...
Shut up. I told you to do nothing...
经我允许你才能做
nothing without asking me first.
闭嘴SB!
Shut the fuck up!
如果他有什么意外...
If anything happens to him...
我会剥光你的衣服...
I will strip you naked...
把你的蛋蛋切下来挂在岗哨上
and hang you by the balls from the watchtower.
- 噢 - 开门
- Heh. - Open the door.
- 卡卡-- - 开门!
- Gaga-- - Now, Vlad!
是他们自做主张...
It was never meant you'd be put out...
让你挨冻, 我深表歉意，查伯先生
in the cold like that, Mr. Chambers. I apologize.
我们已经谈好了，我上擂台，然后重获自由
We had a deal. I fight, I go free.
不，交易是...
No, the deal was...
你赢了你才可以走
you win, you go free.
你知道我被人下药了
I was drugged and you know it.
是的，我知道
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
或许下次你再和博伊卡打的时候...
Maybe next time you fight Boyka...
你要注意挑个可靠的助手了
you should pick a better cornerman.
操你!
Fuck you!
我不干了
There ain't gonna be a next time.
听说我，乔治，其实事情很简单
Listen to me, George. It's very simple.
我挣钱，你挣自由，大家可以双赢
I make my money. You make your exit.
操你!
Fuck you!
操我?
Fuck me?
随意啦
As you wish.
呆在这好好享受吧...
Enjoy the rest of your stay here...
查伯先生
Mr. Chambers.
等等
Hold on.
这次不许下药
No drugs.
无论是我还是博伊卡
Not me, not Boyka.
我和他来场公平的
We fight straight up.
当然
Of course.
你要知道，乔治...
Look, George...
我也不想让你在这多呆，因为……
keeping you here any longer is a bit of a hassle for me.
你太惹人注目，会给我带来不少麻烦
You're, uh, too visible.
所以我想要的是再打一场……
All I want is one more fight.
一场解决问题
One.
菲尔在哪?
And Phil?
Heh.
不必担心菲尔
You don't have to worry about Phil.
他在……钱……恩
Where he is, money...heh...
钱不是理由
Money is not a factor.
我还能为你做什么,查伯先生?
Anything else I can do for you, Mr. Chambers?
有的
Yeah.
还有一件事要麻烦你
I'm gonna need one more thing from you.
乔治?
George?
你知道这棉袄从哪来的?
You know where this coat come from?
我听说从...
'Cause I hear it come from...
一个宣称自己从不帮助别人的混蛋那来的
selfish asshole who never does anything for anyone else.
为什么这样做?
Why?
问那么多干吗?
Why you think?
因为这鸟地方太冷了
It's cold as a motherfucker around here.
我看过你和博伊卡的第一场比赛
You know, George, I saw first fight.
看出点门道
I saw something in first round.
在你的眼中
Something in your eyes.
在你被药迷倒之前
Before you started to look drunk.
说说看，克罗特，我看到了什么?
Ok, Crot, what did you see?
你自己说你看到了什么?
What did you see, George?
Tsk.
好吧
OK.
或许我低估了那小子不少
Maybe I underestimated the guy a little bit.
但是我现在熟悉了他的套路
But I know how he fights now.
下次我不会再吃亏了
And that same stuff ain't gonna work on me a second time.
我要找到制敌之道
I'm gonna figure somethin' out.
是的……你需要有人帮忙
Maybe...you need a little help.
你想帮我，呵呵?
Oh, you gonna help me?
我没打过擂台，乔治
I'm no fighter, George.
但我曾经被训练过如何杀人
But I was once trained how to hurt people.
我对格斗略知一二...
I know a thing or two about grappling...
主要是军队教的近距离格斗术
military close combat.
可能对你有所帮助
Things you might need in this type of fight.
谢谢你的好意，克罗特，我自己能行
You know what, Crot? Thanks, but I'm OK.
一切搏击都由街头打架的实用技术演化而来
Hey, this is all street fighting anyway,
而那是我自小就熟悉的
and that's what I'm from.
我会打败他，重获自由
I'll just go home on his ass.
还有，博伊卡精通的那些混合搏击术...
Besides, all that kickboxing and grappling stuff...
也不过尔尔
- it's overrated. - Aah!
# I move weight like a freight truck, build the muscle #
# You can't escape your fate, we ain't scared to tussle #
Aaah!
# I put the pressure on your offense #
# You can't advance, I'm a pro #
# Hit the bench, bro, you had your chance #
# Do my dance in the end zone, and hone my skill #
# If I don't take it all the way, no one will #
# Get back, you outta line, you outta your mind #
# You outta time, keep searching, brotha #
# How do you find another man #
# As efficient as this machine I am? #
用我的长项打败我
Beat me at my own game, huh?
那我也用你的长项打败你
I'm gonna beat you at yours.
Hmm.
听着，乔治
Now listen, George.
人体就像一个锥型...
Man is like pyramid...
不过是倒着的
but upside down.
你打断他的腿就能解决他
You cut his legs-- Finish.
好的，但我们要怎样做?
OK. How do we...begin?
现在拿我来做实验
Now get on top of me.
不行，你经不起折腾
Sorry, man, I'm just not attracted to you.
太冒险了
Maybe it's the beard.
你想训练还是想开玩笑?
You want to train or you want to joke?
# Bring it on #
# And I'm ready to eat #
# So if you're scared, get outta here #
# Before you get beat #
# Bring it on #
# Yeah, the heat is on #
# You better get your best to the plate #
# Or it be the gong #
# Calculate the magnitude #
# Of the situation you're facing #
# No time for pacing, there's no time for wastin' #
Unh!
这是基本的锁臂术
So this is a basic arm lock.
当你挥拳过来，我抓住你的手
When you punch, I grab.
紧紧锁住
I wrap arm.
用劲，明白吗?
Put pressure, you see?
你可知道那个老头在训练美国人?
You know the old man is training the American?
这能吓住我吗?
Is that supposed to scare me?
他想学什么就学什么
He can learn any fucking thing he wants.
Yaah!
反正他甭想活着离开擂台
He's still not going to leave that ring alive.
# Bring it on #
# Do you accept the challenge? #
# I'm-a test your balance #
- Argh! - # Bring it on #
# You can't stand the violence #
# Bring it on #
# Put your tail between your legs, leave in silence #
- # Bring it on # - Argh!
# You can't handle the heat #
# Bring it on #
不好意思--
Hey, man, sorry. Uh--
没事
No, it's OK.
土豆酿的伏特加（一种烈性俄国白酒）
Potato vodka.
我在卫生间酿的
I make it in my toilet.
我不能喝，我还有比赛要打
No, man, I'm gonna pass.
当然，你正在训练中
Of course, you are in training.
那张照片是怎么回事?
So what's up with the photograph?
很漂亮的一个小姑娘，对不?
She's beautiful, isn't she?
她是谁?
Who is she?
我的侄女
My niece.
她现在快19了
She's almost nineteen, now.
她来探望过你吗?
She ever visit you here?
没
No.
从没来过
Never.
为什么不来?
Why not?
以为她不知道我在这...
She doesn't know that I'm here...
根本不知道我在哪
that I exist.
我也不想她到这来
I never want her to come to this place.
嘿，我只是好奇...
Hey, I was just wondering...
到底发生了什么?
what happened?
你是怎么被关进来的?
How did you get yourself in this place?
当我还在苏联军队的时候...
When I was in the army...
我年轻的弟弟...
my younger brother...
在家门口打劫了党委书记
he robbed party headquarters near our house.
恰好我正休假在家
It happened when I was home on leave.
一天，他过来找我...
He come home one day...
我感到他有话要说
and I see it in his eyes.
他说他犯下了大罪
He tells me he just made a big mistake.
- 你弟弟? - 是的
- Your brother? - Yes.
那么，为什么他没被关进来?
Well, why the hell isn't he here instead of you?
维克托很优秀
Victor was brilliant.
他前程似锦...
He had a future...
还有一个妻子
And a wife.
一个怀孕的妻子
A pregnant wife.
而我?
Me?
只是一个为勃列日涅夫（前苏共主席）卖命的军人
I was only a trained killer for Brezhnev.
所以...
So...
你用你的一生去代他受过
you basically traded your life for his.
不，不
No, no.
刚开始，我只是为弟弟的抢劫罪而判了四年
I-I was given only four years for the robbery.
但是在这儿我饱受折磨
But when I got here they tried to drive me crazy.
忍无可忍，我决定越狱
So finally, I decided to escape.
我逃了两次
I tried twice, actually.
最后一次，与他们打了起来
The second time there was a fight.
我杀了一个警卫
A guard got killed.
但我自己也因为被射中脊椎而瘫痪
I was also shot, paralyzed.
他们把我一人关禁闭
They put me here in solitary.
典型的苏联式折磨
Soviet style.
你知道的，乔治
You see, George?
我接受了现实
I accepted my reality.
这是命啊
This is where I belong.
我会在这老死的
And this is where I will die.
我不明白，克罗特
I don't get it, Crot.
尼古莱
It's Nikolai.
什么?
Huh?
我叫尼古莱
My name, it's Nikolai.
我知道你不理解
And I know you don't get it.
# Oh, yeah #
Argh!
# It's an illusion #
Ugh!
Ow!
- Ow! - Argh!
Argh!
把我的腿抬到你肩上
Now on top of shoulder.
用头压住
Lock with head.
同时使劲摁住膝盖
Now press on top of knee.
用力，乔治
Press, George.
再用力
Harder!
如果我使劲，你的腿就断了
If I press any harder it's gonna break.
也不错，说不定疼痛会让我恢复知觉呢
Good, maybe I start to feel the leg again.
Boyka.
Chambers.
你搞笑吧（短裤上的C.C.C.P是苏联的俄语简称）
You are trippin'.
今晚，我会终结他
Tonight, I settle it forever.
再次打败他...
I beat this man again...
解决一切问题
then there is no question.
我将成为最牛的终极斗士
I'm the most complete fighter in the world.
记住, 乔治...
Remember, George...
比赛结束的时候...
when fight is over...
不要往回看，迅速离开场地
you need to leave fast. Don't look back.
听着...
Listen...
尼古莱，我...
Nikolai, I, uh...
- 我很高兴-- - 不，无需多说
- I'm glad that-- - No, shut up.
打完比赛再说
Stay mean for fight.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
打完再说
I'll see you later.
乔治...
George...
我也很高兴
I'm glad, too.
再一次，欢迎...
Once again, please welcome...
前世界轻量级拳击冠军...
former Heavyweight Boxing Champion of the World...
乔治...
George...
莱斯曼・查伯!
Iceman Chambeeers!
Chambers! Chambers!
接下来，欢迎...
And now, let's welcome...
我们未尝败绩的轻量级搏击冠军...
our own undefeated Heavyweight Champion...
尤里・博伊卡!
Uri Boykaaaaa!
Boyka! Boyka!
Chambers! Chambers! Chambers!
- Boyka! Boyka! - Chambers!
Boyka! Boyka!
开始!
Fight!
Unh!
- Unh! Ah! - Uh!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Argh! Unh!
Ugh!
Argh!
Yeah!
Unh!
- Argh! - Unh!
Argh!
- Unh! Ah! - Uh!
Ugh!
Move in!
Boyka! Boyka!
- Argh! - Yah!
Ugh!
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
Argh!
Ow!
停! 第一回合结束!
Stop! Round's over!
打得不赖，乔治
Not bad for first round, George.
但为何不用你的新招?
But why you don't use your new technique?
我会在适当时候用的
I'm working on it.
博伊卡，让他等着
Boyka, make him wait.
记住，打断他的腿
Remember, take his leg.
Fight!
Unh!
Argh!
Unh! Uh!
Unh! Ugh!
Arrrgh!
Ugh! Unh!
- Argh! - Ow!
Ugh!
Boyka! Boyka! Boyka!
Boyka! Boyka!
Unh!
Ow!
Arrrgh!
Argh!
搞定他!
Take him!
Argh!
听我说，乔治
Listen to me, George.
你必须结果他...
You must finish him...
否则你永远别想...
or you will rot in this stinking hole...
从这个监狱出去
for the rest of your life.
就像我一样!
Like me!
- 好好干!
- Go! - Ugh!
我是冠军！
I am the champion.
他们永远不会让你离开这
They will never let you out of here.
你别无选择，乔治
Do you understand me, George?
你还等什么?
What are you waiting for?
比赛开始
The bell.
Argh!
Ow!
Yaaah!
# You can't advance, I'm the storm at night #
# Bring it on and be ready to fight #
# Do you accept the challenge? #
# Bring it on #
# I'm-a test your balance #
# You can't stand the violence #
- Ow! - # Bring it on #
# So put your tail between your legs and run off in silence #
# Bring it on #
# You can't handle the heat #
# This cannibal is hungry for meat #
# Bring it on #
# And I'm ready to eat, so if you're scared #
# Get outta here before you get beat #
# Bring it on #
Chambers! Chambers!
# Is to shine more bright in the sunlight #
# I'm the storm at night #
# Bring it on and be ready to fight #
# Do you accept the challenge? #
Unh!
Argh! Argh!
Now on top of shoulder.
Argh!
Lock with head.
Press harder!
Fuck you!
Argh!
Press, George.
Harder.
Ugh!
If I press any harder it's gonna break.
I'll kill you, motherfucker!
Aaaah!
- Yes! - Aaah!
Aaah!
Aaaargh!
Argh!
Aah!
别碰我!
Don't touch me!
Chambers! Chambers! Chambers!
Chambers! Chambers!
Chambers! Chambers! Chambers! Chambers!
你发财了
You made a fortune.
呵呵，时来运转
Yeah. I had a feeling our luck would change.
是吧?
Hmm?
Chambers! Chambers!
恭喜你，查伯先生
Congratulations, Mr. Chambers.
我可以离开这了，对吧?
I'm outta here, right?
是的
Yes, you are.
等等
One moment.
这是什么?
What's this?
你应得的
Your cut.
听着，乔治，我也不想...
Listen, George, it was never my intention...
让你呆在这受折磨
to make your stay here so unpleasant.
对不住了 等等
I'm sorry for that. One more moment.
是否介意我们来一张合影?
Do you mind if we take a photo together, me and you?
不是为我，是为了我侄子
Not for me. My nephew.
他是你的超级粉丝
Big fan of yours.
听好了
Let me tell you something.
我永远忘不了你对我做的一切
I'm not gonna forget what you did to me.
永远
Ever.
我还会来找你的
And I will see you again.
这就是我想说的
That's my word.
但是现在...
But right now...
我很高兴能离开这鬼地方
I'd like to get the hell out of here.
当然
Sure.
等等
One moment.
这家伙想干吗？
Where the fuck is he going now?
查伯先生，别犯傻
I wouldn't try anything stupid, Mr. Chambers.
门外全是警卫
There are guards outside.
放松，我只是找你谈谈
Relax, I just need to talk to you about something.
谈什么?
What?
谈一笔交易
I wanna make a deal.
来告别的?
Came to say good-bye, huh?
是的
Yeah.
你打得很好
You did well.
我搞定一切了
I did all right.
那件我送你的棉袄还在?
Do you still have that jacket I got you?
当然
Of course.
我会永远保存他
I will hold on to it forever.
现在，由你决定...
Well, now that's up to you...
但你最好马上穿上它
but you better grab it and put it on right now.
为什么?
Why?
因为，尼古莱...
Because, Nikolai...
有一个18岁的姑娘想见她叔叔
there's an 18-year-old girl who needs to meet her uncle.
而且外面贼冷
And it's cold as a motherfucker out there.
像是做梦啊
I don't know about this, George.
一切会好起来的，尼古莱
It's all right, Nikolai.
你有大把时间忘记过去的一切
You got a lot of time to let it sink in now.
我说，乔治，这是个错误
I'm telling you, George, it's a mistake.
不是
No, it ain't.
我不敢面对她
No, I can't.
你可以
Ah! Yes, you can.
不敢
No, I can't.
去吧！好运！
- Go. - Oh, George.
# Oh #
# I move weight like a freight truck, build the muscle #
# You can't escape your fate, we ain't scared to tussle #
# I put the pressure on your offense, you can't advance #
# I'm a pro, hit the bench, bro, you had your chance #
# Do that dance in the end zone and hone my skill #
# If I don't take it all the way, no one will #
# Get back, you outta line, you outta your mind #
# You outta time, keep searching, brotha #
# How do you find another man #
# As efficient as this machine I am? #
# I was born immortal, to be the king of the sport, a portal #
# Just follow me to the next dimension #
# You get lifted like these plates I'm benchin' #
# Go ahead, put your two cents in #
# Your worries are worthless #
# Takes a strong-like mind to understand my purpose #
# It's to shine more bright than sunlight #
# I'm the storm at night #
# Bring it on, if you ready to fight #
# Bring it on #
# Do you accept the challenge? #
# I'm-a test your balance #
# Bring it on #
# You can't stand the violence #
# So put your tail between your legs and leave in silence #
# Bring it on #
# You can't handle the heat #
# This cannibal is hungry for meat #
# Bring it on #
# And I'm ready to eat, so if you're scared #
# Get outta here before you get beat #
# Bring it on #
# Yeah, the heat is on #
# You better get your best to the plate or it be the gong #
# Calculate the magnitude of the situation you're facing #
# No time for pacin', there's no time for wastin' #
# What, you thought it would be a cake walk? #
# I won't make it easy for you to hate-talk #
# The trash is big #
# No, I couldn't let you do it no longer #
# So I built up mass and my passion is stronger #
# To the point that I need an extra me to hold it #
# So think that you could try #
# But ain't no need to fold it #
# Or bend it any which way, nothing is happening #
# Just me groovin' here, I'm-a keep on rappin' #
# And then the competition has to retire, no other chance #
# Who can do it like I do it? No other voice #
# If you need some help, call the doctor, get some medicine #
# I'll expire you, bring you back to life #
# And make you dead again #
# Bring it on #
# Do you accept the challenge?#
# I'm-a test your balance #
# Bring it on #
# You can't stand the violence #
# So put your tail between your legs and leave in silence #
# Bring it on #
# You can't handle the heat #
# This cannibal is hungry for meat #
# Bring it on #
# And I'm ready to eat, so if you're scared #
# Get outta here, before you get beat #
# Bring it on #
# Show me the money, show me the glory #
# Gimme a second to demonstrate #
# Let me tell you the story #
# Do me a favor, pretend my name wasn't in the street #
# If you my homie #
# You won't have no problem holding this heat #
# If you my enemy, then stay away #
# You gets no love #
# lmagine your soul escaping, just floatin' above #
# Another day, another dollar, earned the paper real slick #
# Ah, it doesn't matter if it's illegitimate #
# Either way we're gonna get what we want and get it quick #
# If you in the way, you feel the contents of this clip #
# I'm not a gangsta, but I know gangstas belong in the dump #
# I'm not a softie, come on, let me see you #
# Show you a chump #
# Not a little boy talkin' big man talk, neither #
# I'm a cold brotha, never catch me without a heater #
# You want drama, I've got it for you like it was Broadway #
# Didn't wanna miss a night, you have to learn it the hard way #
# Bring it on #
# Do you accept the challenge? #
# I'm-a test your balance #
# Bring it on #
# You can't stand the violence #
# So put your tail between your legs and leave in silence #
# Bring it on #
# You can't stand the violence #
# So put your tail between your legs and leave in silence #
# Bring it on #
# You can't handle the heat #
# This cannibal is hungry for meat #
# Bring it on #
# And I'm ready to eat, so if you're scared #
# Get outta here before you get beat #